freetoclassifieds.com 2013-06-05

# Privacy Policy

###  **This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for freetoclassifieds.com**

Because freetoclassifieds.com wants to demonstrate its firm commitment to your privacy, freetoclassifieds.com has agreed to disclose its information gathering and dissemination practices.

freetoclassifieds.com will notify you of:

  * What information is collected from you through the web site;
  * The organization collecting the information;
  * With whom the information may be shared;
  * The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under freetoclassifieds.com control;
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information;
  * How the information is used;
  * What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.

If you feel that freetoclassifieds.com is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you wish to modify information previously given, or have any questions regarding the privacy policy, please contact us.

###  **MINORS**

freetoclassifieds.com does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age.

###  **INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**

freetoclassifieds.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. freetoclassifieds.com collects information from our users at several different points on our web site. freetoclassifieds.com collects information from users responding to ads regarding their Internet provider; this information may include the user's IP address, host name, country of origin and Internet provider being used. This collected information may be shared with the user placing the ad for the sole purpose of assisting this user in determining the validity and legitimacy of the response. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. We may use information collected to promote other affiliate programs, products, web sites and services.

Information about your computer hardware and software is automatically collected by freetoclassifieds.com and may be shared with third parties whose services are used for traffic analysis purposes. This information includes: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by global-free-classified-ads.com to maintain and improve the quality of the service and to generate statistics regarding use of the freetoclassifieds.com site.

Financial information, such as credit card numbers and bank account information, is not collected on our site.

###  **CHOICE/OPT-OUT**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. Please note that participation in certain activities on our web site may be limited if personally identifiable information is not submitted for the user.

###  **LINKS**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that freetoclassifieds.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by freetoclassifieds.com.

###  **DISCLOSURE**

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Agreement. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from our Site.

###  **SITE AND SERVICE UPDATES**

We will send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to the account via e-mail.

###  **NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Home page and use our best efforts to announce via e-mail so all users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will make a reasonable effort to notify users by way of an e-mail. Users have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

﻿
